var readlineSync = require("readline-sync");
const chalk = require("chalk");

var userName = readlineSync.question("What's your name ? ");
console.log(chalk.red("Hi", userName + ", here's a quiz on MCU. Just type the correct option number."));
console.log("  ");

var score = 0;

function quiz(question, options, answer) {
 var userAnswer = readlineSync.keyInSelect(options, chalk.yellow(question));
 if(userAnswer+1 === answer) {
   console.log(chalk.green("That's right :)"));
   score++;
 }
 else {
   console.log(chalk.red("That's wrong :("));
   console.log(chalk.green("The correct option is", answer));
 }
  console.log(chalk.cyan("score =", score));
  console.log("-------------------------------------------");
  console.log("  ");
}

var questionBank = [
  {
    question: "Q.1) Who is Black Pantherâ€™s sister? ",
    options: ["Ramonda","Shuri","Nakia","Okoye"],
    answer: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: "Q.2) What were the three items Rocket claims he needs in order to escape the prison? ",
    options: ["A security card, a fork, and a prosthetic leg","A security band, a battery, and a prosthetic leg","A pair of binoculars, a detonator, and a prosthetic leg","A knife, cable wires, and a prothestic leg"],    
    answer: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: "Q.3) What is the name of the little boy Tony befriends while stranded in the Iron Man 3? ",
    options: ["Harry","Henry","Harley","Holden"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Q.4) The Flerkens who are a race of extremely dangerous aliens, resembles what? ",
    options: ["Cats","Ducks","Racoons","Snakes"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Q.5) What type of doctor is Stephen Strange? ",
    options: ["Cardiothoracic Surgeon","Trauma Surgeon","Plastic Surgeon","Neurosurgeon"],    
    answer: 4 
  },
  {
    question: "Q.6) What fake name does Natasha use when she first meets Tony? ",
    options: ["Nicole Romanoff","Natalie Rushman","Natalia Romanoff","Naya Rabe"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Q.7) What does the Winter Soldier say after Steve recognizes him for the first time? ",
    options: ["Who the hell is Bucky?","What did you say?","What!","I'm not bucky!"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Q.8) Who was the last holder of the Tesseract before Thanos claims it for his Infinity Gauntlet? ",
    options: ["Thor","Loki","The Collector","Ebony Maw"],
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Q.9) In the Incredible Hulk, what does Tony tell Thaddeus Ross at the end of the film? ",
    options: ["That he wants to study The Hulk","That he knows about S.H.I.E.L.D.","That they are putting a team together","That Thaddeus owes him money"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Q.10) What year was the first Iron Man movie released, kicking off the Marvel Cinematic Universe? ",
    options: ["2005","2008","2012","2010"],
    answer: 2
  }
];

for(var i = 0; i < questionBank.length; i++) {
  quiz(questionBank[i].question, questionBank[i].options, questionBank[i].answer); 
}

console.log(chalk.magenta("Your Final score is", score + " out of 10"));
console.log("  ");
console.log(chalk.cyan("Here's the Leaderboard - ")); 
var leaderBoard = [
  {
    name: "Rohit ",
    score: 9
  },
  {
    name: "Sunil ",
    score: 5
  },
  {
    name: "Mahesh Deshmukh ",
    score: 2
  }
];

for(i = 0; i < leaderBoard.length; i++) {
  console.log(chalk.green(leaderBoard[i].name, leaderBoard[i].score));
}

console.log("  ");

var isHighScoreBroken = false;

for(i = 0; i < leaderBoard.length ; i++) {
  if(score > leaderBoard[i].score) {
    console.log(chalk.yellow("Congratulations, you have secured rank", i+1, "on the leaderboard! If want your name on the leaderboard, send me a screenshot of your score. Thank you!"));
    isHighScoreBroken = true;
    break;
  }
}

if(isHighScoreBroken = false) {
  console.log(chalk.yellow("Thank you for playing the quiz! Did you find it too easy or too tough? Let me know :) "));
}
